Josh Gottheil Collection ARC.0150
Library and Archives
Josh Gottheil Collection
Bulk, 1983-1989
1976-2009, undated
ARC.0150
Library and Archives
4.33 Linear feet (1 records carton, 1 Hollinger box, 1 audiovisual box, 1 oversize box)
The Josh Gottheil Collection contains material related to the life and career of Josh Gottheil from the period 1974 to 2009 and includes some undated material, with the bulk of the material falling between the years 1983 and 1989. The collection materials are focused primarily on the Champaign-Urbana alternative and punk music scenes, in which Josh was an active figure from an early age, performing in and promoting local bands and, later, bringing headlining acts to perform in the area. The majority of the collection consists of promotional materials for bands, benefit concerts, and local venues--some that Gottheil promoted or followed personally, and others in which he performed. The types of materials found in the collection include advertisements; calendars; clippings; correspondence; documents, including venue applications, bank statements, contracts, forms, guidelines, and letterhead; printed ephemera such as brochures, flyers, and tickets; fanzines; friends’ memories of Josh; graphic materials in the form of a cartoon, photographs, postcards, posters, and publicity mockups; mailing and guest lists; newspapers; press kits; printouts of blog postings and online articles; a yearbook; and audiocassette recordings, some with CD copies. Artists of note in the collection include ¡Ack-Ack!, Jello Biafra, Bowery Boys, Billy Bragg, the Breeders, Camper Van Beethoven, the Didjits, Tanya Donelly (Belly, Breeders, Throwing Muses), Farmboys, Flaming Lips, Hüsker Dü, the Pixies, R.E.M., the Replacements, Jonathan Richman, and Gottheil’s two bands, the Dangerous Acquaintances and the Dead Relatives. A number of items in the collection relate to the Better Youth Organization, a University of Illinois at Champaign-Urbana student group to promote alternative music; the Leukemia Society of America; the No More Censorship Defense Fund; Record Swap and Record Service, two area record stores; Champaign-Urbana music venues, including the Channing-Murray Foundation, Mabel's, the Thornburn Center, Trito's Uptown, and the Urbana Civic Center; and Gottheil’s two concert promotion companies, Subversive Sounds and Concert One Productions. His impact on the Champaign-Urbana scene can be traced through the wealth of ephemera and other documentation available on his various activities, while his impact upon individuals within that scene is palpable through the articles, memoirs, and correspondence written during his illness and after his untimely death. The collection as a whole provides a glimpse into the management and promotion of local bands, specifically in the Midwest, as well as the career of a very unique musician-turned-promoter.
Better Youth Organization (University of Illinois)
Channing-Murray Foundation (Urbana, Ill.)
Concert One Productions (Firm)
Daily Illini (Champaign, Ill.)
Dangerous Acquaintances (Musical group)
Donelly, Tanya
Fletcher, Elayne
Gottheil, Josh, 1969-1989
Mabel's (Champaign, Ill.)
Michael, Troy
Neuhaus, Tad
News-gazette (Champaign-Urbana, Ill.)
No More Censorship Defense Fund (Organization)
Poulos, Anthony
Richman, Jonathan, vocalist
St. Clair, Katy
Subversive Sounds Productions (Firm)
Trito's Uptown (Champaign, Ill.)
Biographical Note
1974 Gottheil begins studying violin at age 5 with Frances Reedy.
circa 1979 Begins studying percussion with Dennis Wiziecki.
1981 Fall Enters Urbana Junior High School. Joins percussion section of the school band and orchestra. Continues lessons in violin and percussion.
1982 August 28 Performs on the drums at his bar mitzvah.
1982-1983 Forms the Dangerous Acquaintances (DAs) with school friends Baltie DeLey on bass, Ammar Bazzaz on guitar, David Teitlebaum on guitar and vocals, and Gottheil on drums. Becomes the self-appointed “manager” of the DAs, pushing for practices, booking gigs, making flyers, etc.
1983 August 26 DAs perform at Urbana Park District Crystal Lake Pool (Urbana, Ill.).
1983 October 15 DAs perform at a private party in Urbana, Ill.
1983 November 11 DAs and The Edge perform at Junior High Night at the Eagles Club (Urbana, Ill.).
1983 December 9 DAs perform at the Urbana Junior High School Dance.
1984 February 23 Breeders and DAs perform at Channing-Murray Foundation.
1984 May 25 DAs and Breeders perform at the Urbana Civic Center.
1984 August 7 DAs perform for Teen Night at Mabel‘s.
1984 August 10 DAs perform at the Thornburn Center.
1984 August 14 DAs perform for Teen Night at Mabel’s.
1984 August 23 Breeders perform with the DAs at the Urbana Civic Center.
1984 Fall Gottheil enters Urbana High School.
1984 October 19 DAs peform with The Signs and Case Closed at the Urbana Civic Center.
1984 October 26 DAs play a Halloween party.
1984 October 27 DAs perform at the Channing-Murray Foundation.
1984 November 9 DAs perform with Case Closed at the Thornburn Center.
circa 1984 December Gottheil joins new band, The Dead Relatives, formed by lead singer Dave Holtgrave, a graduate student in psychology at the University of Illinois, and including Lorie Buczkiewicz on bass and Bob Droege on guitar.
1985 January 21 Toxic Reasons performs with Dead Relatives for a punk dance at University High Gym (Urbana, Ill.).
1985 February 3 Rock Against Hunger: A Benefit for Ethiopia featuring Fun & Anguish, Reaction Formation, Club Crack, Fake Boys, Breeders, ¡Ack-Ack!, Farm Boys, Dead Relatives, and Krazy Eddies at Illini Union, Room C, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign.
1985 March 9 Blatant Dissent performs with 1096, the Charming Deviants, and the Dead Relatives at University High Gym (Urbana, Ill.).
1985 May 24 Mortal Micronotz perform with Dead Relatives at 805 West California (Urbana, Ill.).
1985 July 15 Rebels and Infidels perform with the Asexuals and Dead Relatives at Illini Union.
1985 September 10 Tex and the Horseheads perform with special guests Dead Relatives at Trito’s Uptown.
1985 September 25 Capitol Punishment performs with Dead Relatives and H.S.R. at Trito's Uptown.
1985 November 26 The Detonators perform with Life Sentence and the Dead Relatives at Ilini Union, Room C.
1985 December 8 Jam for Life featuring The Outnumbered, Nitelife, The Models, Weird Summer, Farmboys, ¡Ack-Ack!, Otis and the Elevators, Dead Relatives, and Electrics at Mabel’s.
1985 December 14 Penguin Dust, The Didjits, Dead Relatives, Red Pajamas, and Just Plain Macarthur perform at Illini Union Room C.
1986 February 10 Descendants perform with Dead Relatives at Illini Union Room C.
1986 March 31 Farm Boys perform with Dead Relatives at Mabel's.
1986 April 5 Toxic Reasons perform with Dead Relatives at the Thornburn Center.
1986 April 15 Glorious Din performs with Dead Relatives at Trito’s Uptown.
1986 May 10 Band Jam on the Quad featuring Generic Error, Illinoize, McWilson Mowo, Cries and Whispers, H.S.R., Blood Brain Barrier, Freeloader, and Dead Relatives at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign Quad.
1986 Spring Gottheil forms Subversive Sounds Productions out of the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign branch of the Better Youth Organization.
circa 1986 Gottheil begins working at Record Swap. Begins to promote concerts with Record Swap, WEFT, and That's Rentertainment.
1986-1987 Subversive Sounds Productions begins promoting bands to perform in the Urbana-Champaign area, including 7Seconds, 1096, Adolescents, Beefeater, Big Black, Bowery Boys, Buckethead, Capitol Punishment, Charming Deviants, Cheetahchrome Motherfuckers, Club Crack, Cries and Whispers, Das Damen, Dayglow Abortions, Dead KCIS, Defoliants, Didjits, Doggy Style, Dough Boys, Flaming Lips, Grey March, H.S.R., IlliNoize, die kreuzen, Life Sentence, Lonely Trailer, McWillson, Mojo Nixon and Skid Roper, Outbreaks, Outnumbered, Pixies, Problem Children, Random Noise, Raw Power, Rhythm Pigs, Royal Crescent Mob, Scab, Scratch Acid, Shakes, Shudder to Think, Sloppy Seconds, SNFU, Th'Inbred, Titanic Love Affair, Toxic Reasons, Transgression, Tugrik Dhugugrik, Urge Overkill, Verbal Assault, and WaTTSBaLDHEaD.
1987 January Gottheil completes the requirements for early graduation from high school and begins taking courses at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaian and Parkland College.
1987 February 8 Subversize Sounds with Jon Ginoli present a benefit for No More Censorship Defense Fund featuring the Didjits with the Outnumbered and Buckethead at Channing-Murray Foundation. Likely the last time Gottheil performs.
1987 Summer Gottheil travels to Israel and Europe.
1987 Fall Subversive Sounds begins collaborating with Anthony Poulos, a promoter from the Chicago area, who had brought bands to the Champaign-Urbana area.
1988 August Gottheil moves to Chicago.
1987-1988 Anthony Poulos and Subversive Sounds Productions begin promoting concerts in the Urbana-Champaign area, including 10,000 Maniacs, Alice Donut, Balancing Act, Billy Bragg, The Connells, Dash Rip Rock, dB's, Didjits, Farmers, Fetchin' Bones, Flaming Lips, Hüsker Dü, Living Colour, Meat Puppets, Mojo Nixon and Skid Roper, Nix 86, Pixies, Schoolyard Truce, Shakes, Michelle Shocked, Soul Asylum, Souled American, They Might Be Giants, Throwing Muses, Titanic Love Affair, and Camper Van Beethoven.
1987 November-1988 June Gottheil is diagnosed with lymphoma and undergoes chemotherapy.
1988 November Gottheil enters Barnes-Jewish Hospital in St. Louis, Mo. for a bone marrow transplant.
1988 October Gottheil, Poulos, and R.J. Abrams create Concert One Productions to promote concerts in the Champaign, Chicago, and St. Louis areas, including 16 Tons, American Music Club, Jane's Addiction, Let's Active, Ministry, Jonathan Richman, Royal Crescent Mob, Semi-Twang, They Might Be Giants, Timbuk3, Titanic Love Affair, and Velvet Elvis. Gottheil is diagnosed with a recurrence of lymphoma.
1989 March 5 Poulos and Abrams organize Concert for a Cure to benefit the Leukemia Society of America and support Gottheil's hospitalization and cancer treatment; Peter Holsapple, Peter Buck, and Robyn Hitchcock perform with Spies Who Surf and Joan Baby at The Cubby Bear (Chicago, Ill.).
1989 April 4 Gottheil dies.
1989 May 14 Throwing Muses perform with Titanic Love Affair, Hot Glue Gun, and The Bowery Boys at Mabel’s to benefit the Leukemia Society of America.
1989 September 28 Flaming Lips perform with Titanic Love Affair and Little Engine at Trito’s Uptown to benefit the Leukemia Society of America.
1989 November 12 Pixies perform with The Zulus at Foellinger Auditorium, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign to benefit the Josh Gottheil Memorial Fund for Lymphoma Research / Leukemia Society of America.
1990 April Record Service 20th Birthday CD release with 20 years of music from Champaign-Urbana, including All-Star Frogs, Appaloosa, Captain Rat and the Blind Rivets, Champaign, Coalkitchen, Elvis Brothers, George Faber and Stronghold, Dan Fogelberg, GAGA, Erin Isaac, Last Gentlemen, Mudhens, Nix 66, One-Eyed Jacks, Otis and the Elevators, Outnumbered, Rave, Screams, and Vertebrats; “Dedicated to Josh Gottheil who would have been 20 also.”
1994 September 23 Localpalooza featuring The Bludgers, Charming Beggars, Cover Band, Jambu River, Moon Seven Times, Soulstice, and Ten Year Old Nirvana at Foellinger Auditorium to benefit the Josh Gottheil Memorial Fund for Lymphoma Research.
1996 October 5 The Bludgers and Room 13 perform at Phi Kappa Theta fraternity house to benefit the Josh Gottheil Memorial Fund for Lymphoma Research.
1998 September 21 Josh’s Jam featuring Luna with Hum, Sarge, and Menthol at Foellinger Auditorium to benefit the Josh Gottheil Memorial Fund for Lymphoma Research.
1997 October 22 Tanya Donelly performs with Lanterna and Space-Age Polymers at Mabel’s to benefit The Josh Gottheil Memorial Fund for Lymphoma Research.
2009 May 24 Play or Pose: The Poster Children perform with The Outnumbered, Lonely Trailer, and Cowboy X at The Highdive (Champaign, Ill.) to benefit the Josh Gottheil Memorial Fund for Lymphoma Research.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Patrons must sign the Acknowledgment of Legal Responsibility and Privacy Rights statement on the Researcher Registration form before using this collection. Band contact information and mailing lists are confidential and, therefore, RESTRICTED. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
Scope and Contents
The Josh Gottheil Collection is organized chronologically, into the different periods of Gottheil’s life and career, usually determined by the band in which he was performing or the production company he was running at the time. The only exception to the chronological organization is the accrual that was added to the collection at a later date, which is first arranged by format and the chronologically. The majority of the collection is arranged and described at the item-level, as this was how the materials were described upon receipt. For those materials not inventoried at the item-level, original order was maintained. Oversize materials are stored out of sequence due to size and condition.
Custodial History
The Josh Gottheil Collection was received by the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame Museum, Inc. as gifts from Fred and Diane Gottheil on August 10, 2011 and August 7, 2012.
Accruals
An accrual, including contracts and audio recordings, is located at the end of the collection.
Separated Materials
Commercial audio recordings have been transferred to the library collection. Please search for the "Josh Gottheil Collection" in the library catalog for a list of donated titles. If you are unable to find what you are looking for, consult the Library and Archives staff to ensure these materials are available.
Biafra, Jello; Black Flag (Musical group); Bragg, Billy; Breeders (Musical group); Camper Van Beethoven (Musical group); Civic Center (Urbana, Ill.); Dead Relatives (Musical group); Descendents (Musical group); Didjits (Musical group); Farmboys (Musical group); Flaming Lips (Musical group); Gottheil, Diane; Gottheil, Fred; Gottheil, Josh, 1969-1989; Hüsker Dü (Musical group); KALX (Radio station: Berkeley, Calif.); Leukemia Society of America; Mabel's (Champaign, Ill.); Mississippi Nights (St. Louis, Mo.); Pixies (Musical group); R.E.M. (Musical group); Replacements (Musical group); Richman, Jonathan, vocalist; Thornburn Center (Urbana, Ill.); Timbuk 3 (Musical group); Toxic Reasons (Musical group); Trito's Uptown (Champaign, Ill.); WEFT (Radio station: East Central Ill.); ¡Ack-Ack! (Musical group); Alternative rock music; Calendar; College student newspapers and periodicals; Compact discs; Concert agents; Mass media and publicity; Newspapers--Local editions; Newspapers--Local editions--Directories; Photographs; Postcards; Press kits; Printed ephemera; Punk rock music; Record stores; Rock concerts; Yearbook; Zines
- Early Years, 1974, 1981, 1982
  - Color photograph of Gottheil with percussion teacher, Dennis Wiziecki, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1, Object 1)
  - Color photograph of Gottheil performing at percussion recital, 1981 Fall (Box 1, Folder 1, Object 2)
  - Color photograph of Gottheil at his Bar Mitzvah with Jon Kaufman, 1982 August 28 (Box 1, Folder 1, Object 3)
  - Color photograph of Gottheil at his Bar Mitzvah with Lisa Gottheil and Garret Jakobsson, 1982 August 28 (Box 1, Folder 1, Object 4)
- Band Ephemera and Clippings, 1983-1988, undated
  - Champaign-Urbana, 1983-1987, undated (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Miscellaneous, 1983-1988, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - From Gottheil's bedroom walls, with photographs, 1984-1985, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Outside Champaign-Urbana, 1984-1987, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Dangerous Acquaintances, 1983-1984
  - Correspondence to Gottheil from Lisa Majdiak, Special Events Coordinator, Urbana Park District, 1983 August 15, 1983 August 29 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 1-2)
  - Urbana Park District performance agreement for Crystal Lake Pool, 1983 August 26 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 3)
  - Invitation to party at Kim Tebussek's, featuring the Dangerous Acquaintances, 1983 October 15 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 4)
  - Receipt for sound equipment for Tebussek party from C. V. Lloyd, 1983 October 15 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 5)
  - Flyer for Junior High Night at the Eagles with Dangerous Acquaintances and the Edge, 1983 November 11 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 6)
  - Performance contract between Dangerous Acquaintances and Urbana Junior High School Student Council, 1983 November 17 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 7)
  - National Bank of Urbana savings account statement for the Dangerous Acquaintances, 1983 December 30 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 8)
  - Receipt for sound equipment for Junior High Night concert from Klaus Radio, 1983 November 4 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 9)
  - Gottheil's drawing of Dangerous Acquaintances performing, circa 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 10)
  - Flyer for Breeders and Dangerous Acquaintances at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1984 February 23 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 11)
  - Flyer for Dangerous Acquaintances and Breeders at Urbana Civic Center (3 designs), 1984 May 25 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 12-14)
  - Photographic reproduction of black and white photo of Dangerous Acquaintances: Gottheil, Steve Coombs, David Teitlebaum, Baltie De Ley, 1984 Summer (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 15)
  - Fictitious letter (written by Gottheil) to Gottheil from Tom P. Harris, EMI America Recording Studios, 1984 July 19 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 16)
  - Letter to Gottheil from Luanne Thulstrup, Recreation Secretary, Urbana Park District, with guidelines for building rental (Thornburn Center), 1984 July 19 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 17)
  - Photographic reproductions of black-and-white photographs of Dangerous Acquaintances performing (6 images), 1984 August 7 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 18-23)
  - Poster for Teen Night/Young Adult Night at Mabel's with the Dangerous Acquaintances (2 designs), 1984 August 7 (Box-folder OS1-1, Object 1-2)
  - Flyer for Rock and Roll with Dangerous Acquaintances at Thornburn Center, 1984 August 10 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 24)
  - Poster for Teen Night at Mabel's with the Dangerous Acquaintances, 1984 August 14 (Box-folder OS1-1, Object 3)
  - Flyer for Breeders with Dangerous Acquaintances at Urbana Civic Center, 1984 August 23 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 25)
  - Letter to Gottheil from Luanne Thulstrup, Recreation Secretary, Urbana Park District, 1984 October 15 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 26)
  - Flyer for Dangerous Acquaintances with The Signs and Case Closed at Urbana Civic Center, 1984 October 19 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 27)
  - Receipt for stage rental at the Urbana Civic Center, 1984 October 19 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 28)
  - Ticket for Dangerous Acquaintances with The Signs, Case Closed at Urbana Civic Center, 1984 October 19 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 29)
  - Poster for Violent Femmes, 1984 October 20 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 79)
  - Invitation to Halloween party featuring Dangerous Acquaintances, 1984 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 30)
  - Flyer for Dangerous Acquaintances at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1984 October 27 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 31)
  - Poster for the Psychedelic Furs at Huff Gymnasium, 1984 October 29 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 15)
  - Jennings, Ron and Ben Weaver. "UHS Students Form Bands." Echo, 73, no. 2, 1984 November 1 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 49)
  - Flyer mockup for Dangerous Acquaintances with Case Closed at Thornburn Center, 1984 November 9 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 32)
  - Photocopy from Urbana Junior High yearbook, Reflections on Paper, pages 6-7, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 33)
  - Dangerous Acquaintances band rules, circa 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 34)
  - Dangerous Acquaintances list of songs, circa 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 35)
  - Dangerous Acquaintances lyrics, circa 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 36)
  - Flyer mockup for Dangerous Acquaintances, circa 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 37)
  - Program for Vicious by Denis Spedaliere, circa 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7, Object 38)
- Dead Relatives and Better Youth Organization, 1985-1986
  - Pasted down and loose local newspaper clippings, regarding Toxic Reasons and Dead Relatives at Mabel's, and Blatant Dissent, Charming Deviants, 1096, and Dead Relatives at University High gym, 1985 January 19, 1985 March 8 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 1-2)
  - Flyer for Toxic Reasons, with special guests Dead Relatives, at University High gym (Better Youth Organization presentation), 1985 January 21 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 2)
  - Poster for Toxic Reasons with special guest Dead Relatives at University High Gym, 1985 January 21 (Box-folder OS1-1, Object 4)
  - University of Illinois at Urbana - Champaign Request for Use of University Premises and Facilities form, filled out by the Better Youth Organization, 1985 January 21 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 4)
  - The Daily Illini, 1985 January 23 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 50)
  - Paaswell, George. "I've Got to Do Something to Change Things." The Daily Illini [color photocopy], 1985 January 24 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 16)
  - Wood, Paul. "Eight hours for Ethiopia." The Champaign-Urbana News-Gazette Weekend, 1985 February 1 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 1)
  - "C-U performers supplement Band Aid's Ethiopa funds." The Daily Illini Directory, 1985 February 1-1985 February 7 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 5)
  - Flyer for Rock Against Hunger at Illini Union, Room C, 1985 February 3 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 6)
  - Better Youth Organization advertisement with copy of Paaswell, George. "Stereotypes don't apply here: punk promotoers are trying to do 'something positive.'", circa 1985 February 3 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 7)
  - Flyer for Blatant Dissent, 1096, Charming Deviants, and Dead Relatives at University High gym (Better Youth Organization presentation), 1985 March 9 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 8-9)
  - Flyer for Mortal Micronotz, with special guests Dead Relatives, 1985 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 10)
  - Form for Urbana Park District Thornburn Center Chaperone Guidelines (completed by Better Youth Organization), 1985 May 30 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 11)
  - Flyer for Adrenalin O.D., with Hate, at Thornburn Center (Better Youth Organization production), 1985 June 6 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 12a-12b)
  - Flyer for Rebels and Infidels, Asexuals, and Dead Relatives at Illini Union (Better Youth Organization presentation), 1985 July 15 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 13-20)
  - Flyer for Rhythm Pigs at Illini Union Rooms A and B (sponsored by the Better Youth Organization), 1985 July 18 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 21-22)
  - Brochure for Tex and the Horseheads, with special guests Dead Relatives, at Trito's Uptown, 1985 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 23)
  - Flyer for Tex and the Horseheads, with special guests Dead Relatives, at Trito's Uptown, 1985 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 24)
  - Review of the Dead Relatives, and an interview with the Dead Relatives A.C. Gazette, 1985 September 13, 1985 December 15 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 25)
  - Dead Relatives stickers (4) and invoice for print job, 1985 September 24 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 26-30)
  - Flyer for Capitol Punishment, with the infamous Dead Relatives and HSR, at Trito's, 1985 September 25 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 31)
  - Flyer for the Detonators, Life Sentence, and Dead Relatives at Illini Union Room C (Better Youth Organization presentation), 1985 November 26 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 32)
  - University of Illinois at Urbana - Champaign Request for Ground Permit form, and Illini Union Rental Agreement form, 1985 November 26 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 33-34)
  - "Hey, get this." The Champaign-Urbana News-Gazette Weekend, 1985 December 6 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 2)
  - "Local bands to hold 13-hour benefit for AIDS victims," The Champaign-Urbana News Gazette, 1985 December 7 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 35)